{
    "id": "d59fc50ad3694415935883e4df39dba8",
    "title": "Conjunctions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will be ready ................... the time you return.",
            "description": "By means not later than.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5e81da0c29d4a55814b06043e4ec41e"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must finish the job ...................... you leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "by",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b6e6c902743437886c002e515b67a2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I screamed ..................... I saw the snake.",
            "description": "The moment means as soon as.",
            "answers": [
                "a moment",
                "the moment"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "64920cd9da6d43299b94a364586f06e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hurt myself .................... I was hiking yesterday.",
            "description": "While and when are used to talk about something that happened on one occasion.",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "whenever",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "781cc8deec554ee7b3f2d71bbf9c77a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hurt myself ..................... I go hiking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "when",
                "whenever"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "84407a993cdf46c9a13c76bc554903a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be ready when you ....................",
            "description": "When both clauses refer to the future, we use a simple present tense in the subordinate clause.",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "will arrive",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c3a3b0878f2d4ed89b4c4cca4c176c3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I stayed an extra day .............................. I could see more places.",
            "description": "So that indicates purpose. ",
            "answers": [
                "hence",
                "so that",
                "therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "73526c3268fc48fcb5fdd0853ab5ea8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... in doubt, read the instruction manual.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ebfc0fa17fa24de19297dd9f31678f37"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cook on low flames ....................... the soup is ready.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "up to",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f2a2f05a20ed4d09aed53300dfb9441d"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... you know, I was never interested in this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "That",
                "So"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd92855457124329b07a99dba6775b50"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ...................... she married was an old friend of mine.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses both that and whom can be used to refer to people. ",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8a2939d80e8642c9aa700b05f9107454"
        },
        {
            "question": "She always thanks me for the all favors ....................... I do her.",
            "description": "A that -clause is more common after words like all or any. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b39eeb135a3748a8bb0a182a9b6fa3ff"
        }
    ]
}